Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hello.
You have to remember to lock the door.
And good morning.
- WOMAN: Dad? - Hey.
Hi. What's up?
I needed to borrow a vase.
Okay. That's fine.
Oh. Those are for Mom's birthday?
Yes. Her favorite flowers.
I'm going to put them. uh. on her headstone.
They're beautiful.
- 'Morning. beautiful. - Hi.
Hi. Angelo. You're here early.
Yeah. I got a big day today.
I got to go to Rochester.
- Oh. cool. - For what?
It's office supplies service sales convention.
It's. uh... I told you about this.
Don't you remember?
Right. Sorry. Baby brain.
Yeah.
I have my grant proposal
presentation today. too.
Well. that's outstanding. How's it going?
Good. Really good.
I think I have a real shot at this one. so...
- Yeah. - Yeah.
What about you? What are you up to today?
Um. classes in the morning.
and then parent-teacher conferences all afternoon.
Maria. I'm so sorry.
I need the car today. I completely forgot.
Well. I can take you to work.
- Really? - Yeah.
That way I can spend more time with my daughter.
When you're ready. I'll meet you in the car.
- MARIA: Yeah. - Good luck today.
Yeah. You. too. Sorry.
You got this.
- Love you. - Good luck.
I know it's tough for me to be away on your mother's birthday.
Dad. I'll be fine.
It's just that I miss her so much.
- Okay? - Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Thanks. Dad.
She'd be so proud of you.
Thanks.
Hey. guys. Good morning.
Good morning. Ms. Maria.
- Are you ready? - Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow. Have a good day.
MARIA: Bye. Dad. Yeah.
MAN: How we doing. Angelo?
The target's approaching.
Black SUVs.
Mr. Zhang. we have your usual table ready for you.
MAN: Target's walking in.
ZHANG: It's her birthday.
My daughter wants to be near the stage.
MAITRE D': No problem. This way. please.
- Crap. - ANGELO: What?
Well. he's moving to a different table.
nowhere near the window.
Hello? What do you want to do?
ANGELO: I'm going to have to come in.
He's got guys on the door. okay?
You can't get a weapon in here.
ANGELO: Get me a reservation.
And when I get in there.
get him in the bathroom.
Reservation?
Yes. Connor. Table for three.
BODYGUARD: We got his car key.
- Mind waiting at the bar? - Certainly.
ZHANG: Go. Li. Go. Li. Go.
Hey. Watch where you're going.
What are you doing?
Zhang should be with you in about 20 seconds.
MAN: He's not alone.
What are you so upset about? It all worked out.
You should've known it was the daughter's birthday.
What am I. God? How would I know that?
Let's get going.
TOUR GUIDE: exteriors in A Bronx Tale.
Now. the Bronx is one of New York City's five boroughs.
Historically. it does have a reputation for being
a rougher neighborhood.
but truth be told. it's a very vibrant cultural place.
Here's your cut.
You know how many people took a swing at Zhang down the years
and died trying?
How'd he do?
What do you want me to say?
He's your nephew. Dutch.
He's got a mouth on him. but who doesn't at his age?
You didn't.
Always a cagey bastard. even in the schoolyard.
That's because you talked enough for both of us.
Yeah.
Well. we play to our strengths. Let's eat.
You hear about Al Beal?
Yeah. I heard he got busted.
Yes. he did. In Philly.
Al gets home. and there's a chopper over the house.
Boom! He's surrounded.
Cops and feds everywhere. Sniffer dogs.
Freaking bomb squad in the garage.
Whole street's taped off.
"Freeze! Hands in the air!" All the cop talk. right?
Then. bam!
SWAT pin him to the ground.
ARs to his head.
Al looks up. totally straight. totally sincere.
and he says. "Is this about the alimony?"
Al Beal. ladies and gentlemen.
ANGELO: Just a taste for me.
I got to watch my cholesterol.
What are you. a dietician now?
No. Doc says I got to up my good protein.
I got to eat fish. chicken and tofu.
Tofu.
Imagine being the guy who invented tofu.
He'd almost be as rich as you.
With my wife and kids?
You're lucky you never decided to do the wife and kids thing.
Yeah. Well. what can I say? I like my own company.
Still time. buddy. Still time.
ANGELO: Hey. buddy.
Yeah. That's right.
Originals.
Took me seven years to track these down.
Reggie Jackson.
Your 12-year-old self would've killed me for these.
Do you want them?
Huh?
Come on. What. you think I'm going to give them to you
just because you're my brother?
Nice doing business with you.
How's he doing. Jane?
Hey. Uh. well.
I found him in the lobby last night at 4:00 a.m..
wearing his best suit.
And he spoke to me for the first time in weeks.
He did? What'd he say?
Something about the two of you going fishing on the Hudson...
on a raft made of old tires.
- Is this real? - Yeah. We did.
And the fish could always hear us coming. couldn't they. Mike?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
ANGELO: He's getting worse.
JANE: He has good days and bad.
Look. Ideally. he would've started treatment when he was
forgetting his ATM PIN and losing track of his keys.
Yeah. Hmm.
Hey.
I think that he would really benefit from this.
If you fill in the consent part.
then I can take care of the rest.
Thank you. Jane.
- You're welcome. - Appreciate it.
Okay.
MARIA: Hey. Dad. Hope you made the sale in Rochester.
Don't forget. Dinner at 7:00.
Hey. How are you?
Forget the code?
You okay. Mr. Doyle?
Mr. Doyle?
- Yeah. Fine. Thanks. Corey.
COREY: You left your bag out here in the hallway. Mr. Doyle.
You got a bowling ball in here?
Thank you.
Hey. Joe. Any chance you ran those plates
on the blue truck yet?
JOE: It came back stolen.
But it wouldn't be Zhang's guys. Not their vibe.
Okay.
Ah.
That's not it.
Son of a bitch.
ANGELO: So. the guy I whacked in Newark last year
was Carl Mosher's younger brother.
Uh-huh.
You knew?
You let me kill the brother
of a Bertoletti captain and you didn't tell me?
I found out after.
There are crime families. and then there are the Bertolettis.
It's complicated.
Different fathers. different last names.
Yeah. but they're brothers.
That part's pretty simple.
Were you going to tell me?
Not without good reason.
Does Carl Mosher coming after me count?
He was tailing me this morning. or hired someone to.
Well. maybe you're getting rusty. Angelo.
What's he going to find out? You live like a monk.
You go to bed at 9:00 p.m.. okay?
Don't worry about it. I'll make some calls.
Just put some guys on my brother's place.
- Michael? - Yeah.
I killed this guy's brother.
I don't want him coming after mine.
Okay. Okay. I'll send Wilson and McManus.
But you. you just stay away from Mosher. okay?
I'll take care of it.
Like you took care of it the last time?
Let me be real clear. okay? You work for me.
You'd be on the street if it wasn't for me. I made you.
There's no extra-curricular nothing.
You're not going near Mosher.
You're not starting a beef with the Bertolettis. all right?
Now. I've always given you your space.
your freedom. whatever.
What you do. where you go. that's none of my business.
You're a dark horse. Solo art.
I respect that.
I love that.
But you got no family at home to worry about.
no offence to Michael.
I do. I very much do.
So. you cross me on this.
and you're on your own.
DUTCH: Pick up. Pick up! Let's go.
ANGELO: Okay. Hey. Pay attention.
I'm teaching you the recipe.
Why do I need the recipe when I have you?
There'll be three soon. Maybe four's a crowd.
Don't be silly.
Hey. you want to come to my scan tomorrow?
Is Jeff cool with that?
Yeah. Why wouldn't he be?
He can be a little sensitive.
Hey. Make a fuss of him. okay?
- Did he get the grant? - Mm-hmm.
Third place. and it was state-wide. Dad.
ANGELO: Hey. Jeff. How's the beer?
Oh. Uh. it's nice.
Yeah. nice.
It's a little nutty for my taste.
but. you know. nice.
Yeah. I picked it up yesterday in Rochester.
Did you make a sale?
Canon C5 copier times two.
- Nice. - That's great.
I hear you scored. too. Jeff?
Uh. yeah. Third place. You know. they love the app.
So. how much is the grant?
$3.000.
Well. that should buy a lot of diapers.
Well. um. so he has to spend money developing the product.
JEFF: Yeah.
I have to show full accounting. so...
Well. that's good.
JEFF: Let me get this thing out of the office.
I need to take it to the shed. so. um...
Sure. Let me get the door for you.
- Oh. thank you. Sorry. - No worries.
- Watch the back there. - Yeah.
You're about to have a baby.
and you have a husband who doesn't work.
He works all day long!
Unpaid.
If it's unpaid it's a hobby. Maria.
How do you think Steve Jobs got started?
Do I need to point out the obvious?
Oh. my God. That is so defeatist.
It's realistic.
What if none of his eggs hatch?
What if. for whatever reason. he doesn't get the...
He's a good man. Dad. and I love him.
Okay?
That's what matters.
ANGELO: Time for a birthday toast.
To Leah.
- JEFF & MARIA: To Leah.
And so. Leah is starving. so we went and got a burger.
Then. in the middle of lunch. her water breaks.
JEFF: What? Really?
ANGELO: The doctor was completely wrong.
JEFF: Oh. my gosh. I never knew that.
ANGELO: We go right back to the hospital. Four hours.
- Hey. - Yeah.
ANGELO: I messed up.
I mean. all this time. keeping everything separate and clean.
and now. someone is there in Hudson Springs
from the other life. and I don't know how they found out.
Dutch. he tells me. "Stay away from Mosher."
But how do I do that? Huh?
I mean. what am I not seeing?
I worked so hard keeping Maria safe.
Nothing is going to jeopardize that.
You would tell me. right. if I wasn't thinking straight?
I'm not going to do anything crazy.
but you got to help me find Carl Mosher.
You want a bigger role in our jobs. right?
Then you got to earn my trust.
He's a bag man for the Bertolettis. okay?
Cash collection. He hangs around their bars.
Favorite place?
Most nights. he's at Silverstrand.
Dutch's favorite place. There you go.
- MARIA: Hey. Dave. - DAVE: Hey.
Um. come in. There's cake.
Oh.
Thank you. but I can't.
Come on. Have a piece.
I'm here on duty.
Oh. Not a social call. then?
I'm looking for your dad.
Uh. yeah.
He. uh... He's at home.
I just came from there.
No sign of him.
Hey.
Slow day for Hudson Springs' finest?
Hey. Jeff.
I'll let you good folks get some rest.
- Good night. - Good night.
Okay. Um. is it about Mom?
Just something I need to talk to your dad about.
What? At 10:00 at night?
What is it?
I'll catch up with him tomorrow.
- Good night. - 'Night.
- Angelo! - Hey.
I've been telling this guy
to try this place for years.
and he's always like.
"No. no. no. I got to get my beauty sleep.
Mint tea. herbal bath. bed."
What kept you away all these years? My personality?
Yeah. I guess so.
I always thought you were a massive creep.
Guess you won't be buying me a drink. then?
- No. I got an early flight. - Yeah? Too bad.
You ain't going nowhere.
Let's get some shots here!
JEFF: Where do you think your dad is?
No idea.
You think he has a girlfriend?
If he did. I'd know.
He tells me everything.
I mean. evidently not.
He's probably just afraid you'd have a problem with it.
What?
I'd be over the moon if he found someone.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I mean. if it was the right someone.
I'm going to get another round.
Attaboy! All right. I want to see you on that dance floor.
All right.
I like how you handled that guy upstairs.
Yeah. Well. he's the kind of guy
who thinks it's okay to knock my girls around
and then show up like nothing happened.
Why let him back?
He's on the payroll.
Want me to take care of him?
Bold talk.
What can I get you to drink?
Mezcal. Want to join me?
Ah. no drinks for the staff.
Ah.
You know what? Screw it. I'll join you.
Tough day?
Long day.
So. what do you do?
I like to know who's in my club.
I'm a hit man.
But I only kill bad people.
In that case...
What do you really do?
I sell photocopiers.
You must've sold a lot of printers.
It's. uh. copiers.
Bathroom?
Yeah. It's right in there.
I hope that's not the guy from the club.
No. He lives in Brooklyn.
You sure?
Carl lives right behind the dump in Bay Ridge. appropriately.
It's uh. Nicky. by the way.
Angelo.
Want to get breakfast?
I know this great place across the park.
Love to. but I got to go to work.
I'm going to get some water.
There's a bottle in the fridge.
Nicky?
Hey.
MARIA: Just calling to remind you about the scan.
Like I'd forget.
I'm not that old yet.
Hey. I got to go.
I'll call you on my way home. okay?
- Okay. - All right. Bye-bye.
ANGELO: You made a mistake following me.
You killed my brother!
Who else knows about Hudson Springs?
What you talking about?
I don't know nothing. man.
DOCTOR: There's the heart.
- The head. - Sorry. Sorry.
- Hey. - Heya.
You're white as a sheet.
Oh.
That's a nasty cut on your neck.
Oh. yeah. That's a...
Almost decapitated by a very large printer.
It's a long story. Sorry I'm late.
What about the gender?
It's hard to say from this angle.
He just sat up.
It's a boy?
- It's a boy. - Oh!
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
- Congratulations. - Oh. my God!
- MARIA: Oh. - JEFF: Are you happy?
MARIA: Yeah. Yes!
- Oh. my... Oh. - Look at him.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Fellows. I'm going to take off. Something came up.
He's out. Earl's out.
When?
DAVE: Two weeks ago.
He killed my wife.
What happened to eight years. no parole?
His cellmate was a mobster who ran his mouth.
It looks like Earl testified against him
and the feds got him out as a thank-you.
I'm sorry. Angelo.
- Hey. - You okay. Dad?
Yeah. Just another middle-management sap
who can't find their ass with both hands.
Successful trip to the baby store?
Yeah. He made a start. We got the bassinet.
Except you need a bassinet and a crib. apparently.
It's a racket.
- It'll be fine. Jeff. - No. He's right.
But I'm going to take care of the crib.
Cookie's. Same place I got yours.
Oh. thanks. Dad.
MARIA: Shame you didn't hang on to it.
Hmm?
My crib.
Oh. hey. You know.
don't look at me.
JEFF: You know. apparently.
I was a really sweet baby
until bedtime. and then I became Scarface.
ANGELO: You okay? You okay?
Stay with her!
No!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org